freeplaymusic.com 2016-04-10

# Freeplay Music | Welcome | The best music library on the planet!

**Privacy Policy**

This document was last updated on April 26th, 2013.

Freeplay Music, LLC. is committed to respecting the individual privacy of its users and contributors. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing this website, you acknowledge and fully understand our Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described herein. 

Anyone under the age of 18, may only use this site and its services in conjunction with and under the supervision of their parents or guardians, and with express permission from us. For this reason, we ask that anyone under the age of 18 should not submit any personal information through our site. This website collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our web server logs, information provided by you the user, and with cookies.  Any information we obtain from you, except as otherwise stated herein, will only be viewed by us. We do not send spam to visitors to our site. We do not sell our users and contributors email addresses or business information to anyone for any reason whatsoever. Information provided by you through optional, voluntary submissions is used only to provide more comprehensive services to our users. 

Any financial information we collect from you is used only to bill you for the services you requested and/or purchased and any applicable fees that you are required to pay. If you purchase by credit card, the information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be needed in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting. Under some circumstances we may require some additional financial information, including, without limitation, your billing address. We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary to do the following:

·       To fulfill your request for services;

·       To protect ourselves from liability;

·       To respond to a legal process, comply with law, or when legally compelled to do so; or

·       In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.  

_Web Server Logs_  

When you visit our website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

·       Your Internet protocol address;

·       The kind of browser or computer you use;

·       Number of links you click within the site;

·       State or country from which you accessed the site;

·       Date and time of your visit;

·       Name of your Internet service provider;

·       Web page you linked to our site from; and/or

·       Pages you viewed on the site.

_Cookies_  

This site uses cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality. You may accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then this may disable some of the functionality of our website.  

_Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site_  

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link to our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.  

_Your Consent_  

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Freeplay. We have the discretion to update this Privacy Statement. If we change our privacy policy, we will change the date above and post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. 

If you have further questions or comments, please direct them to questions@freeplaymusic.com
